<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>New bug(maby hidden feature) with nuclear waste</title>
    <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/new-bug-maby-hidden-feature-with-nuclear-waste/1339</link>
    <description>I have a let&#39;s play world with 4,000 power plants (nuclear power plants) I hit 4 googles of uranium waste (not plutonium) and I haven&#39;t put down a single-particle accelerator for plutonium power but once I hit 4 googles of uranium waste I started getting plutonium wast so I went to the nuclear setup and all my uranium fuel rods where now plutonium fuel rods and all my other uranium things where now plutonium things and I don&#39;t have any of it attached to a blender or particle accelerator.
once again I am not sure if it is a bug or hidden feature</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 17:26:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>General</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/new-bug-maby-hidden-feature-with-nuclear-waste/1339.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>New bug(maby hidden feature) with nuclear waste</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@logan_jordan Logan Jordan]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/logan_jordan">@logan_jordan</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I have a let’s play world with 4,000 power plants (nuclear power plants) I hit 4 googles of uranium waste (not plutonium) and I haven’t put down a single-particle accelerator for plutonium power but once I hit 4 googles of uranium waste I started getting plutonium wast so I went to the nuclear setup and all my uranium fuel rods where now plutonium fuel rods and all my other uranium things where now plutonium things and I don’t have any of it attached to a blender or particle accelerator.<br>
once again I am not sure if it is a bug or hidden feature</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/new-bug-maby-hidden-feature-with-nuclear-waste/1339/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/new-bug-maby-hidden-feature-with-nuclear-waste/1339/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 17:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-post-1339-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/new-bug-maby-hidden-feature-with-nuclear-waste/1339.rss">New bug(maby hidden feature) with nuclear waste</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
