<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>What&#39;s up, It&#39;s been a while</title>
    <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/whats-up-its-been-a-while/1038</link>
    <description>It&#39;s been a while sense I worked on my mod. I couldn&#39;t get it completed. So I guess it just sat for a long time. I guess that&#39;s why I never released it. 

I wanted to add some kind of Minecarts to the game. That anyone could unlock in Tier 3. It&#39;s just too complex for me to do. So I guess I&#39;ll have to come up with a new mod name. Anyway I&#39;m still have issues with Materials and Textures. I have all ways had a hard time getting my machines to look some thing like a machine. 

I wanted to know if any part of the modding has been updated. Is there a new starter project. I don&#39;t even know what version of that I even have. 

Thanks to everyone that has helped me in the past.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 09:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Modding</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/whats-up-its-been-a-while/1038.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s up, It&#39;s been a while</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@iceman11a Iceman11a *]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/iceman11a">@iceman11a</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>It’s been a while sense I worked on my mod. I couldn’t get it completed. So I guess it just sat for a long time. I guess that’s why I never released it.</p>
<p>I wanted to add some kind of Minecarts to the game. That anyone could unlock in Tier 3. It’s just too complex for me to do. So I guess I’ll have to come up with a new mod name. Anyway I’m still have issues with Materials and Textures. I have all ways had a hard time getting my machines to look some thing like a machine.</p>
<p>I wanted to know if any part of the modding has been updated. Is there a new starter project. I don’t even know what version of that I even have.</p>
<p>Thanks to everyone that has helped me in the past.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/whats-up-its-been-a-while/1038/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/whats-up-its-been-a-while/1038/1</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 09:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-post-1038-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/whats-up-its-been-a-while/1038.rss">What&#39;s up, It&#39;s been a while</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
