<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Light It Up - Deleted Lights on Failed Backup Recovery?</title>
    <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/light-it-up-deleted-lights-on-failed-backup-recovery/709</link>
    <description>Hi there, I hope all is swell..
I realize the error of my ways but need help seeing if there is a solution! And/Or - Report a potential issue when recovering from a backup save file. (Server-Host to different Server-Host) - Loading the .Sav - I failed to load Light it Up (got every mod but this one on the new server) - Played in daylight for a few hours (made progress) - nightfall hit and we realized no lights?!?! - I have now installed Light It Up on the new server which has about 3hrs of IRL progress we don&#39;t want to lose. One of our buddies put A LOT of work into the lighting schemes and I don&#39;t want to have lost the mod that made the game fun for him... any way to recover if one .sav had the mod - got loaded without the mod - saved as an auto-save - loaded the mod postpartum - now no lights not ~ even the options exist.. ..is this a mod that can&#39;t be added to a pre-existing game? - by that standard, technically my game existed 3hrs without it and now I don&#39;t have the options despite installing the mod - Any Help?? - Precious Work at Stake! - Plz and Thx! - TYIA - E² | Minvox
#LightItUp #modding-help:bug-reports #recovery #dedicatedserver #severmigration #usererror</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 06:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/light-it-up-deleted-lights-on-failed-backup-recovery/709.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Light It Up - Deleted Lights on Failed Backup Recovery?</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Eric_Ewing Eric Ewing]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/eric_ewing">@Eric_Ewing</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi there, I hope all is swell…<br>
I realize the error of my ways but need help seeing if there is a solution! And/Or - Report a potential issue when recovering from a backup save file. (Server-Host to different Server-Host) - Loading the .Sav - I failed to load Light it Up (got every mod but this one on the new server) - Played in daylight for a few hours (made progress) - nightfall hit and we realized no lights!!! - I have now installed Light It Up on the new server which has about 3hrs of IRL progress we don’t want to lose. One of our buddies put A LOT of work into the lighting schemes and I don’t want to have lost the mod that made the game fun for him… any way to recover if one .sav had the mod - got loaded without the mod - saved as an auto-save - loaded the mod postpartum - now no lights not ~ even the options exist… …is this a mod that can’t be added to a pre-existing game? - by that standard, technically my game existed 3hrs without it and now I don’t have the options despite installing the mod - Any Help?? - Precious Work at Stake! - Plz and Thx! - TYIA - E² | Minvox<br>
<span class="hashtag">#LightItUp</span> <a class="hashtag" href="/c/modding-help/bug-reports/13">#<span>modding-help:bug-reports</span></a> <span class="hashtag">#recovery</span> <span class="hashtag">#dedicatedserver</span> <span class="hashtag">#severmigration</span> <span class="hashtag">#usererror</span></p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/light-it-up-deleted-lights-on-failed-backup-recovery/709/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/light-it-up-deleted-lights-on-failed-backup-recovery/709/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-post-709-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/light-it-up-deleted-lights-on-failed-backup-recovery/709.rss">Light It Up - Deleted Lights on Failed Backup Recovery?</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
