<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Advanced Logistics and the framerate</title>
    <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/advanced-logistics-and-the-framerate/766</link>
    <description>Hi all,
I&#39;ll try to explain my problem with my poor english.
I&#39;m playing on the EA 125236, Core I7 8700 RTX2060 16Go ... ... ... it&#39;s OK
I have about 15 mods installed (moar, farmer, refined power, etc etc).
Since i use advanced logistics for all my splitting system, when I laugh the game, i lose 10 fps all 2 minutes and my computer&#39;s fans screams. if i  reload the game, idem, the good framerate fall 
inexorably.
I tried remove and add all my mods one by one, so i&#39;m sure it&#39;s this mod the problem.
I&#39;m disappointed... Imagine, the efficiency of parallel splitting with the serial building. It was perfect!
Im surprised that no one talk about this problem before. i though that i&#39;m not alone.
So this is my bug report.
Have a nice day

Ps: I forgot something maybe important with this problem, when the framerate falls and the cpu burn, the satisfactory task use 95% of the CPU, without the advanced logistics mod, it usually turns around 20%</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 06:03:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Bug Reports</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/advanced-logistics-and-the-framerate/766.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Advanced Logistics and the framerate</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Hugo_les_bons_tuyaux Hugo Les Bons Tuyaux]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/hugo_les_bons_tuyaux">@Hugo_les_bons_tuyaux</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hi all,<br>
I’ll try to explain my problem with my poor english.<br>
I’m playing on the EA 125236, Core I7 8700 RTX2060 16Go … … … it’s OK<br>
I have about 15 mods installed (moar, farmer, refined power, etc etc).<br>
Since i use advanced logistics for all my splitting system, when I laugh the game, i lose 10 fps all 2 minutes and my computer’s fans screams. if i  reload the game, idem, the good framerate fall<br>
inexorably.<br>
I tried remove and add all my mods one by one, so i’m sure it’s this mod the problem.<br>
I’m disappointed… Imagine, the efficiency of parallel splitting with the serial building. It was perfect!<br>
Im surprised that no one talk about this problem before. i though that i’m not alone.<br>
So this is my bug report.<br>
Have a nice day</p>
<p>Ps: I forgot something maybe important with this problem, when the framerate falls and the cpu burn, the satisfactory task use 95% of the CPU, without the advanced logistics mod, it usually turns around 20%</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/advanced-logistics-and-the-framerate/766/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/advanced-logistics-and-the-framerate/766/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 21:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-post-766-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/advanced-logistics-and-the-framerate/766.rss">Advanced Logistics and the framerate</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
