<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipe Copier Mod</title>
    <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/recipe-copier-mod/1124</link>
    <description>I think this should be available free at the beginning. Or made available when I first get foundations. I am on another playthrough, but since this is so expensive I still can&#39;t afford it.
Edit: Finally was able to research it. But I still think it should be mostly free so it can be used when I get foundations. I usually don&#39;t need it until then.

About new feature added with version 0.0.5: 
Copy mode is now &#39;toggleable&#39; by clicking the right mouse button.
Is the Hand Tool still needed for this? Or can I just right click when I am near the machine?

Edit: I get it now. Can you add the information about right clicking to change modes to the &quot;How to use it&quot; section? Thanks.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:56:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Modding</category>
    <atom:link href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/recipe-copier-mod/1124.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Recipe Copier Mod</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@JamieRCHI Jamie]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/jamierchi">@JamieRCHI</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>I think this should be available free at the beginning. Or made available when I first get foundations. I am on another playthrough, but since this is so expensive I still can’t afford it.<br>
Edit: Finally was able to research it. But I still think it should be mostly free so it can be used when I get foundations. I usually don’t need it until then.</p>
<p>About new feature added with version 0.0.5:<br>
Copy mode is now ‘toggleable’ by clicking the right mouse button.<br>
Is the Hand Tool still needed for this? Or can I just right click when I am near the machine?</p>
<p>Edit: I get it now. Can you add the information about right clicking to change modes to the “How to use it” section? Thanks.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/recipe-copier-mod/1124/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/recipe-copier-mod/1124/1</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 22:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-post-1124-1</guid>
        <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/recipe-copier-mod/1124.rss">Recipe Copier Mod</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
