<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suggestions &amp; Ideas - SMR Forums</title>
    <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/c/general/suggestions</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Suggestions &amp; Ideas&#39; category Got ideas for mods? Maybe some suggestions for SMR or forums?</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:53:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://forums.ficsit.app/c/general/suggestions.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Lower coal consumption, if power consumption is not 100%</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@yuyaryshev Yuyaryshev]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/yuyaryshev">@yuyaryshev</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>The Biomass Burner has “the resource consumption is automatically lowered”.<br>
I was wondering:</p>
<ul>
<li>Is there any mod that enables you to build a setup that simulates this behavior?<br>
Say a belt splitter that stops if the accumulator charge is above 90% and starts if it’s below 105?</li>
</ul>
<p>Or</p>
<ul>
<li>Is there a mod that has generators with this property? (“the resource consumption is automatically lowered”)</li>
</ul>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/lower-coal-consumption-if-power-consumption-is-not-100/1542">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/lower-coal-consumption-if-power-consumption-is-not-100/1542</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1542</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/lower-coal-consumption-if-power-consumption-is-not-100/1542.rss">Lower coal consumption, if power consumption is not 100%</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Request: More lighting sources (with sample pictures)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Sathapana_Rongthong Sathapana Rongthong]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sathapana_rongthong">@Sathapana_Rongthong</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Due to the game’s limited types of lighting sources and all being too large, it’d be very nice if we have more options for interior and exterior lighting designs. It’s impossible to do indirect lighting designs or light stripes and even though some mod contains a 1m wall with lights, it doesn’t reflect the actual light on other surfaces so that can’t be counted as a lighting source because it doesn’t light up that space.</p>
<ul>
<li>Downlight, lamps, ceiling, wall, floor, or light stripes for designing indirect lightings</li>
</ul>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d.jpeg" data-download-href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d" title="2021-12-09%2022_38_57-Untitled-1_%20%40%20150%20%25%20(RGB_Preview)%20copy"><img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d_2_690x469.jpeg" alt="2021-12-09%2022_38_57-Untitled-1_%20%40%20150%20%25%20(RGB_Preview)%20copy" data-base62-sha1="FaMK9dOt8i41ObjzsQYgGEAz6t" width="690" height="469" srcset="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d_2_690x469.jpeg, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d_2_1035x703.jpeg 1.5x, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/04a7811a189643e2d731fe75a1a7a91a249bc53d_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">2021-12-09%2022_38_57-Untitled-1_%20%40%20150%20%25%20(RGB_Preview)%20copy</span><span class="informations">1100×749 612 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>all individual pictures in link below<br>
<a href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1XblEFq7IquJjLCRQWe1t26-VkyGl1oh2?usp=sharing" class="onebox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1XblEFq7IquJjLCRQWe1t26-VkyGl1oh2?usp=sharing</a></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/request-more-lighting-sources-with-sample-pictures/1505">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/request-more-lighting-sources-with-sample-pictures/1505</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1505</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/request-more-lighting-sources-with-sample-pictures/1505.rss">Request: More lighting sources (with sample pictures)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>TC MOD IDEA: Tiberian Forge (Satisfactory/C&amp;C)</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Orphiex Orphiex]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/orphiex">@Orphiex</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>So I’m not a modder, for Satisfactory or otherwise. Unfortunately, a brainworm has crawled inside my skull and manifested into a mod idea that just won’t leave me alone. So I commit it to digital text here, in the hopes that it will infest some other poor sod and leave me be.</p>
<p>On the other hand, I need to put it out there in an interesting way, otherwise it won’t be exorcised. So here we go:</p>
<h1>===================================<br>
SATISFACTORY / COMMAND &amp; CONQUER:<br>
TIBERIAN FORGE</h1>
<p>"Good afternoon, Engineers. You are all here because you volunteered for this detachment; on behalf of GDI, humanity and life itself, I salute you and thank you for your dedicated and loyal service.</p>
<p>"This mission is both severely divergent from operational procedure and hazardous in the extreme. Nevertheless, needs must; given the lack of options available at this point in time, this course affords the greatest chance of saving this world from the encroachment of Tiberium. While all of you have been briefed on the mission, I will reiterate the salient details for the record.</p>
<p>"At 0245 hours shipboard time two days ago, Scout vessel <em>Andronicus</em> of the GDI Extrasolar Exploratory Corps moved into orbit around the life-bearing planet designated “Massage-2(AB)B” and began scans of the planet’s surface. It was at this time that the saboteur struck; a Brotherhood of NOD infiltrator among the crew was captured in an attempt to destroy the ship by detonating a suborned missile within the armament bays. The bridge Weapons Officer was able to spot the access breach in time and disable the warhead remotely.</p>
<p>"I… almost wish the saboteur had succeeded in his attempt. His contingency plan was… is… far worse. While the warhead itself was disabled, the missile was not, and before he was captured, he launched it at the planet below… carrying a shard of active Tiberium. High-intensity scans are already showing weak Tiberium emission frequencies from the point of planetary impact. In other words, the planet has been contaminated… and if nothing is done, it will be consumed as Earth was.</p>
<p>"The <em>Andronicus</em> is not equipped with the necessary materiel for full-scale Tiberium remediation; the only option is for the ship to return to GDI Command and report the need for a Reclamator detachment. However, every day’s transit is a day in which Tiberium is free to spread through the biosphere of a virgin world. This is unacceptable. Hence, this mission, for which you, the brave men and women of GDI’s Engineering Corps, have volunteered.</p>
<p>"Your mission is simple: abatement, containment and if possible eradication of Tiberium on the world below. You will deploy to the planet by orbital drop pods; unfortunately, we have no field units to deploy with you. You will have to make use of the tools available to you, especially your Field Constructors, to assemble the structures, hardware and materials needed to suppress the spread of Tiberium.</p>
<p>“Good luck, and may God be with you all.”</p>
<p>============================</p>
<p>This is basically a proposal for a Total Conversion multiplayer mod that radically changes the game’s objectives. The players are on a clock; the longer the game goes on, the more the Tiberium spreads and the more dangerous the world becomes. Players start with the majority of blueprints and gear unlocked, and their suits have built-in immunity to gas and radiation… but Tiberium is an environmental hazard all its own, and any fauna that survive Tib exposure become more deadly.</p>
<p>I’m under no illusions that a mod like this would be anything other than massively difficult to make; while some of the code in the game might be adaptable (e.g. the Radar Tower’s scanning pattern could maybe be used to calculate the spread of Tiberium per hourly tick), overall it would probably be a complete nightmare to code something like this. Still, I hope this inspires somebody to build <em>something</em>.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/tc-mod-idea-tiberian-forge-satisfactory-c-c/1496">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/tc-mod-idea-tiberian-forge-satisfactory-c-c/1496</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1496</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/tc-mod-idea-tiberian-forge-satisfactory-c-c/1496.rss">TC MOD IDEA: Tiberian Forge (Satisfactory/C&amp;C)</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Menu Adjusting Mod Idea</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@MdosTV Mdos Tv]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/mdostv">@MdosTV</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>I think a nice addition to the mod market is a mod that can allow you to adjust the placement of the “Hands” and “Body” slots. Got a lot of mods that add more slots, which causes overlapping if you try to use too many of them. Would really like to still have all those slots and be able to access them.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/menu-adjusting-mod-idea/1410">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/menu-adjusting-mod-idea/1410</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 03:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1410</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/menu-adjusting-mod-idea/1410.rss">Menu Adjusting Mod Idea</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Suggestion] mk8 pipe+ mod</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Robert_James Robert James]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/robert_james">@Robert_James</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Can anyone make a pipe mod for each tier of pipe from mk2 pipe of 600m3 to mk3 1200m3 to mk4 2400m3 to mk5 4800m3 to mk6 9600m3 to mk7 19200m3 and mk8 38400m3. I don’t like being limited to 300m3 to 600m3 where my machines push more then that none over clocked.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 4</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-mk8-pipe-mod/1355">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-mk8-pipe-mod/1355</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1355</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-mk8-pipe-mod/1355.rss">[Suggestion] mk8 pipe+ mod</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mod idea will make ausom sink so much easyer</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@logan_jordan Logan Jordan]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/logan_jordan">@logan_jordan</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>I know I have been posting a lot presently but that its because I have mod ideas, bug’s I have found, and general questions.<br>
I am in a ticket race with my brother in the ausom sink and we are allowed to use mods. But there is one mod that I found but was outdated the Ausom points X100 ( mod link <a href="https://ficsit.app/mod/CTbhnCnW8zWWGG" rel="nofollow noopener">https://ficsit.app/mod/CTbhnCnW8zWWGG</a> )  and I was wondering if someone could make a mod like this and or reach out to the mod dev  and update it if allowed and I want to make my own mods so I don’t have to post these stupid forums all the time about mod ideas but I don’t know how yet I am trying to find a non-gibrish guide( i can’t find one that  makes any sense)</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/mod-idea-will-make-ausom-sink-so-much-easyer/1347">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/mod-idea-will-make-ausom-sink-so-much-easyer/1347</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 14:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1347</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/mod-idea-will-make-ausom-sink-so-much-easyer/1347.rss">Mod idea will make ausom sink so much easyer</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Foundations/walls etc Whit internal Power cable</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Markku_Palviainen Markku Palviainen]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/markku_palviainen">@Markku_Palviainen</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Has anyone else had an idea about foundations that had internal Power lines build into.</p>
<p>I have been founding myself thinking about something like this:</p>
<p>Foundation 8X4, with direct power line: cost 6 concrete and 1 cable.<br>
Foundation 8x4, with crossed power line: cost 6 concrete and 2 cable.<br>
Foundation 8x4, cable outlet Up, which you can use, for example, as a source for a normal electrical pole</p>
<p>this could be used in walls etc.</p>
<p>If there is already Mod like this out, i would love to get a link for it.</p>
<p>thanks in advance, best regards<br>
Satisfactory novice engineer<br>
Stonevall</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/foundations-walls-etc-whit-internal-power-cable/1223">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/foundations-walls-etc-whit-internal-power-cable/1223</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 17:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1223</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/foundations-walls-etc-whit-internal-power-cable/1223.rss">Foundations/walls etc Whit internal Power cable</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Ancient/Overgrown Factory Buildings</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Joel_Stead Joel Stead]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/joel_stead">@Joel_Stead</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Ancient Type:<br>
Charred and broken ladders, platforms with signs that they have worked for massive amounts of time without servicing. Lots of grease,rust  and charring on the outside with dents and cracks visible here and there.</p>
<p>Overgrown Type:<br>
Similar to above but with vines, grass, sand, gravel dirt, mud etc piles here and there and up ladders and through the platforms. Cracks and Rust as well here and there to show the machinery was abandoned.</p>
<p>I am looking for a variety of machines/platforms with textures / models to try show an abandoned or very old and overworked factory.</p>
<p>Some possible examples of options:</p>
<ul>
<li>Normal speed / normal power usage. (Basically for looks but no functional change but with a variety of degrees of damage visible) <em>default idea</em> but allowing for other changes for making the game more challenging such as the below.</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<ul>
<li>1/4 speed with 1.75 times power usage required as base value. (Heavy damaged)<br>
For example a miner missing most the mining rods, broken power connector, massive damage to casing, badly worn and damaged drill head, badly damaged engine sparking and cracked with rust and old everywhere)</li>
<li>1/2 speed with 1.5 times power usage required as base value. (Moderate damage)<br>
(Moderate damage to drill head, arcing power connector, engine stuttering, some rubble, cracks and rust over most the machine.)</li>
<li>Normal speed with 1.25 times power usage as base value.<br>
(Light damage but with faulty power connection, rubble and dirt clogging the drill bits)</li>
</ul>
<p>Additional foundations and walls with similar features would be awesome as well to go with the theme.</p>
<p>( Satisfactory has in the description that there were only a few successful landings, but definitely doesn’t specify a time period in which they happened, and with the way we can clip foundations, walls into everything I though of expanding it to show abandoned or old exploration [{especially with doggos always bringing me nuclear waste barrels <img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/images/emoji/twitter/stuck_out_tongue.png?v=9" title=":stuck_out_tongue:" class="emoji" alt=":stuck_out_tongue:"> }] )</p>
<p>What do you think of the idea?</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/ancient-overgrown-factory-buildings/1186">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/ancient-overgrown-factory-buildings/1186</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 08:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1186</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/ancient-overgrown-factory-buildings/1186.rss">Ancient/Overgrown Factory Buildings</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Global Grid Placment</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Adventure4Life Adventure4 Life]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/adventure4life">@Adventure4Life</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>One of the most anoying things when i build my factories is aligning all the foundations. I like to build all over the place, but I really dislike when I try to link to factories together and the foundations do not slot together correctly. So I tend to build these massive “construction lines”.</p>
<p>What I do is place my 1st block… then if I want to build elsewhere I build from that block all the way to the other place, then delete the “construction line”. Now the factory I am building at the new location will link up if I ever do that as it is built off the same “grid”.</p>
<p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4.jpeg" data-download-href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4" title="111"><img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="111" data-base62-sha1="yPLtrbfA5KITce8hpUWwwyMPztW" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4_2_690x388.jpeg, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/f423ed2a95a583d63b9294658ebb8df866f690f4_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">111</span><span class="informations">2304×1296 348 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div> <div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188.jpeg" data-download-href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188" title="222"><img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="222" data-base62-sha1="kRNrq7JKsHpRRasPUNamBQgG7ck" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188_2_690x388.jpeg, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/924049273aea949fc90cd590839cd00300acd188_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">222</span><span class="informations">2304×1296 291 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Here is my new save were I am working on my Iron Mines. I built a base on top of the cliff and then draw my “construction lines”… build down… and now I have built my new foundations in a way so every factory I build will be aligned to the same foundations… so they can all link up perfectly if I build a road or a buss or w/e.</p>
<p>Anyway…</p>
<p><strong>The Suggestion</strong></p>
<p>I think a great mod would be a way to automate this. You could build a foundation and select it… now when you build it uses that foundation to “set the grid”. So your new foundation you place all alone somewhere “snaps” as if it is next to a foundation.</p>
<p>You could make it a tool you hold maybe so the global snapping thing only happens if you are holding it… and it saves the “source block” so you do not need to select a source block each time.</p>
<p>I’m not a modder, I am sure you guys would know the best way to implement it… the goal would be to remove the need for all these construction lines. Which are a pain to buld and annoying to remove.</p>
<p>Thanks…  for your consideration!</p>
<p>PS - I am not the best communicator, if you have any questions please let em know and I can clear things up.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 4</p>
            <p>Participants: 4</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/global-grid-placment/1134">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/global-grid-placment/1134</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1134</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/global-grid-placment/1134.rss">Global Grid Placment</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Download queue for SMM</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Joshua_Fowler Joshua Fowler]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/joshua_fowler">@Joshua_Fowler</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>A simple download queue for SMM would be useful, especially for those who have slower internet. Not  downloading mods simultaneously, just sequential in the order they came in.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 3</p>
            <p>Participants: 3</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/download-queue-for-smm/1074">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/download-queue-for-smm/1074</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 18:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-1074</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/download-queue-for-smm/1074.rss">Download queue for SMM</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Dynamic wall conveyor</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sky_zuma Skyzuma]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sky_zuma">@sky_zuma</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa.jpeg" data-download-href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa" title=""><img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa_2_690x265.jpeg" alt data-base62-sha1="iNCjjLApH9SF2iiCf3G4xOfk7Ds" width="690" height="265" srcset="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa_2_690x265.jpeg, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa_2_1035x397.jpeg 1.5x, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/83c2fd4c7398725ab3a20ae19fcb5d72ff097efa_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename"></span><span class="informations">1372×528 478 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>its possible to create an dynamic wall entry for conveyor or an conveyor wall “hole” like pipeline wall hole to place it on normal walls? i know there are mods with no collision but i like to see the entry for the lift / conveyor belt. Ive many many places like this between two foundations <img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/images/emoji/twitter/frowning.png?v=9" title=":frowning:" class="emoji" alt=":frowning:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/dynamic-wall-conveyor/966">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/dynamic-wall-conveyor/966</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 20:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-966</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/dynamic-wall-conveyor/966.rss">Dynamic wall conveyor</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Escalators mod?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SextonKing Sexton King]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sextonking">@SextonKing</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Fixed function sizes, say go up only across 2 8m foundations. A sort of blending of conveyor belt fixed to a frame with a staircase frame encasing it. Snap the top or bottom to the end of a foundation, the other half auto snaps to the corresponding bottom far edge or nearest grid snapping point on that block. Can even snap to go up to doorways and gate walls. Doesn’t need power but might have a hefty iron plate, motor and rubber cost. A slimmer alternative to spiral staircases but smoother than ladders. Let it have a simple UI you access and hit a button labeled for “UP” or vice-versa for “DOWN.” Cannot be connected to conveyor belts to act like lifts, ONLY for personal movement from floor to floor.<br>
<img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/07b16292d12caa62ba83495977e771c6ecf33c5d.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="163o3x3sJwho56cU28kOS5SlwpT" width="190" height="266"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/escalators-mod/954">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/escalators-mod/954</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 06:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-954</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/escalators-mod/954.rss">Escalators mod?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>“Iris” Sphincter Doors/Access Hatches</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SextonKing Sexton King]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sextonking">@SextonKing</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Kind of like you see in the lower decks of the first “Alien” movie or in other sci-fi movies, or the mechanics of how hypertubes already open and close. A high-tech-looking square-framed Mechanical Iris doorway.<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/24272d3a1bed9a00da4a6b56b21cb403664f2de7.jpeg" data-download-href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/24272d3a1bed9a00da4a6b56b21cb403664f2de7" title="image"><img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/24272d3a1bed9a00da4a6b56b21cb403664f2de7.jpeg" alt="image" data-base62-sha1="59P7IO9HgFrCBHXdz2JaUuJmp0z" width="690" height="388" data-small-upload="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/24272d3a1bed9a00da4a6b56b21cb403664f2de7_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">image</span><span class="informations">1280×720 55.4 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>It could be mounted in full size to an 8x8 vertical area like a massive stargate-looking affair, or a smaller one could be about quarter-foundation size (2mx2m diameter) and come in 1,2,4m depths to use like mechanical access corridor batches.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/iris-sphincter-doors-access-hatches/953">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/iris-sphincter-doors-access-hatches/953</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 06:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-953</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/iris-sphincter-doors-access-hatches/953.rss">“Iris” Sphincter Doors/Access Hatches</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>“Smart Beacons” Mod?</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@SextonKing Sexton King]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sextonking">@SextonKing</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>I know this wouldn’t be a gigantic world-shaking thing, but what about a “Smart Beacons” mod that had some similar capability as, say, X-3 Signs mod? More a smoother QOL type of function.</p>
<p>Like I mean: imagine you want to make a surveying trip to explore a new biome and mark out all the Copper and Iron Nodes to start getting a rough plan of what’s out there and where to start building.</p>
<p>You lay down a beacon, and instead of having to go into its UI and manually title and color-code or manually go about equipping it to a hand slot To drop it, you could hit a key (like “M” for “marker”) and call up the Smart Beacon UI.</p>
<p>There you’d have your little library drop down menu of previously created formats, select the type of beacon you want to leave (maybe “Copper Pure”), hit “OK” and then just click on the node and boom—formatted beacon is placed and humming.</p>
<p>Similar UI options could be as you see in other typical mods—editable key bindings, option to ignore build cost—but maybe you could also have an option to add certain auto-format to the beacon’s name (like how when you alter mass files in Photoshop and it asks if you want to automatically add numeric increments to the default name for all the files).</p>
<p>Perhaps the mod could offer an alternate color selector—plug in an RGB or Hex code and it‘ll do the tricky conversion to HSV for you, no more fiddling with the selector that can sometimes be such a pain to narrow down to a decimal value using the slide bar. No more guesswork, you type in and boom it does the rest of that task for you.</p>
<p>So you go and select your previously saved “Copper Pure” setting, and the mod now will place a beacon that is already color coded, says “Copper (Pure) -01” and the next one you place will be auto-numbered “-02” and so on. You might never have to individually edit the beacons at placement ever again.</p>
<p>Further refinement could be to auto format and append the game world coords into the beacon name of you select that option as well. “Copper (Pure) 01 (x/y/z values)” so you also get that much more functional use out of beacon information (“Look, those two pure coppers are similar elevation, let’s plan for a raised build platform to bridge them.”)</p>
<p>Imagine just tweaking your perfect beacon formats back at base, and from there on anytime you find the node you click, select, click, and boom you’re done and move on. It could be a matter of minutes to beacon-marker an entire biome.</p>
<p>Let’s say further that you want to instead use beacons as a way to very preliminarily ‘sketch’ out the possible path for a later road or railway and you want the path kept as straight as possible but without messing with laying down a bunch of foundations that may snap the beacons to less than ideal points. You want to build a path that works with the terrain but still kept fairly orderly and efficiently laid down.</p>
<p>The beacons could have a hologram option in the UI (call it “Next Beacon Hologram Path”). Click it, and now every beacon you place will have a faint hologram arrow pointing to it extended from the last beacon you placed, up to say 50m. This gives you a simple indicator to help keep your placements in a decent orderly fashion even though you’re working with the natural terrain (the hologram shuts off immediately upon placing the next node).</p>
<p>Now when you go back and check the Map, a clear path of these designated beacons helps you further plan your attack on constructing the next big transport line</p>
<p>Maybe even a further option you can turn on/off for “one click pickup” so just clicking on the beacon picks it up; a quick “click and done” ‘method similar to how you can one-click interact with Item Hopper or Dispenser mods.</p>
<p>Get back to base and open up your map, and there are all your nodes with proper coords (especially altitude), their purity, and a quick scan to tell you how many of each there are.</p>
<p>The mod could work fine with just vanilla beacons, but I guess if a dev <em>wanted</em> to go really crazy they could create a new beacon model (Mk2, call it a Proximity Beacon) to complement the mod, maybe with an optional KMart blue light special flasher on its top that comes on when you come within x meters (great for if you leave fog on).</p>
<p>Have an “Approach Warning” setting in the UI that if an enemy spawns within range of it, the light flashes red instead of blue. Maybe with a thicker or taller shaft that is auto-painted to match its color. This way when you’re approaching at night or other low-visibility conditions, you can still spot the blue flash telling you where your destination is…and a red flash will tell you to expect some fluffy tailed bulls or alpha spitters waiting nearby.</p>
<p>Build cost could be adjusted to keep it balanced (Proximity Beacon requires steel beam, rubber and an AI limiter or High Speed Connector but creates a 2m high color-coded beacon with high-visibility flashing light dome top, no power source required.</p>
<p>Or could it be possible to add the Mk2 beacons to the Object Scanner’s list of scannable things if you haven’t unlocked Map yet?</p>
<p>That way you don’t have to blind ping, you could select “Pure Nodes” on the Scanner and if it shows a high indicator in the same direction as your latest ping, even without a map you can at least tell if it’s a Pure or Normal node you’re marching towards, if you’ve previously beacon marked it.</p>
<p>The more I think on it, a “Smart Beacons” mod could be one of those little ones that doesn’t shake the whole game but at least just helps you spend a little less time messing with a useful but monotonous function. Takes beacons from a rather awkward little stick in the mud to dynamic, active tools for surveys and resource management on the large scale.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/smart-beacons-mod/952">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/smart-beacons-mod/952</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 05:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-952</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/smart-beacons-mod/952.rss">“Smart Beacons” Mod?</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Show Radar Tower Range</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Florian_H Florian H ]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/florian_h">@Florian_H</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Dear Modders,</p>
<p>Is there a way to do a mod to show the range of a radar tower after its placed?<br>
For example a circle or some kinde of green field arround the tower.</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/show-radar-tower-range/939">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/show-radar-tower-range/939</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 19:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-939</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/show-radar-tower-range/939.rss">Show Radar Tower Range</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Subway / Underground Station</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sky_zuma Skyzuma]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sky_zuma">@sky_zuma</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>hello,</p>
<p>its possible to create this? i have an area with many, many platforms on a: “ground &gt; quater pipe &gt; 8xX foundation [ 8x4 gap from " FOUNDATIONINDUSTRIES” ] &gt; inverted quater pipe &gt; 8xX foundation [ split foundations from " FOUNDATIONINDUSTRIES" &gt; way for pipes ]" ~ 32 m high &gt;&gt;&gt; the max hight need to be 30 - 35 m … if is possible to transform the original stations to an half of this and the freight-stations with an front- / side-loader-system or any other function.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/subway-underground-station/864">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/subway-underground-station/864</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 15:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-864</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/subway-underground-station/864.rss">Subway / Underground Station</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Suggestion] Splitters and Mergers with auto covered conveyor</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@YOUCEF_HAMDANI Youcef Hamdani]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/youcef_hamdani">@YOUCEF_HAMDANI</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Hello, When you place a conveyor lift next to a machine/splitter/merger you will get that covered conveyor.It will be <img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/images/emoji/twitter/kissing_heart.png?v=9" title=":kissing_heart:" class="emoji" alt=":kissing_heart:"> nice, if we have this option for splitters and mergers.<br>
            </p><div class="onebox imgur-album">
              <a href="https://imgur.com/a/ggH6T9q" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">
                <span class="outer-box" style="width:600px">
                  <span class="inner-box">
                    <span class="album-title">[Album] Imgur</span>
                  </span>
                </span>
                <img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/34827c280764dc1c5ea9567fbf7e294df6c50b8c.jpeg" title="Imgur" height="315" width="600">
              </a>
            </div>

            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-splitters-and-mergers-with-auto-covered-conveyor/850">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-splitters-and-mergers-with-auto-covered-conveyor/850</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 07:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-850</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-splitters-and-mergers-with-auto-covered-conveyor/850.rss">[Suggestion] Splitters and Mergers with auto covered conveyor</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Basic building blocks</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@sky_zuma Skyzuma]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/sky_zuma">@sky_zuma</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>hello, iam new and no native english speaker … but i missed a few basic modifications like:</p>
<p>Quater pipe with a door</p>
<p>an 4x4 [ half one of an 8x4 ] / 4x8 [ 8x4 vertical ] foundation [ placed on top of an quater pipe and or between a quater pipe and an inverted quater pipe ]</p>
<p>wall-like [ idl the wall skin [ or a wall with the foundation skin without any border-line] ] foundation [ 1x8? 1x4? 1x2? ] to snap on the edge of any foundation to build a way between on a 8x4 foundation or any other</p>
<p>quater-corner quater pipe inverted [ placed on the edge of a quater pipe line instead of an inner-corner quater pipe] + in addition foundations to build an curved areal like normal quater-corner quater pipe [ for an railway system ]</p>
<p>edit:</p>
<p>an underground train station … the half of the normal station with an side / front load system instead of the top load - perfect for a area like: quater pipe &gt; inverted quater pipe &gt; foundation 8x4 &gt; tunnel &gt; undergrond train station / system</p>
<p>more in the future <img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/basic-building-blocks/836">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/basic-building-blocks/836</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 13:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-836</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/basic-building-blocks/836.rss">Basic building blocks</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Stack Overflow problem with mobile miner and handslot</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Torsten_Kolling Torsten Kolling]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/torsten_kolling">@Torsten_Kolling</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>I apologize, my english is really bad.</p>
<p>Stackable mobile miners are a problem with Stack Overflow. If I pick up the stack in the hand slot and drop it on an ressource node, the entire stack becomes to one miner. Even after taking it up it’s just one miner.</p>
<p>I hope I could describe the problem clearly</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/stack-overflow-problem-with-mobile-miner-and-handslot/732">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/stack-overflow-problem-with-mobile-miner-and-handslot/732</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 13:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-732</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/stack-overflow-problem-with-mobile-miner-and-handslot/732.rss">Stack Overflow problem with mobile miner and handslot</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>[Suggestion] Prebuilt conveyor belt curves</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Paolo_Moretti Paolo]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/paolo_moretti">@Paolo_Moretti</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>I think it would be great to have some prebuilt conveyor curves, e.g. mk1 belt 90 degree, mk1 belt 45 degree, mk1 belt 180 degree, and so on…<br>
I find really difficult to align multiple parallel belts and make sure they all have the curve and distance between them:<br>
<div class="lightbox-wrapper"><a class="lightbox" href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/original/1X/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a.jpeg" data-download-href="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a" title="20200623222219_1"><img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a_2_690x388.jpeg" alt="20200623222219_1" data-base62-sha1="vMCj2MpoZ5xSpfvpaMTbLS3KxAu" width="690" height="388" srcset="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a_2_690x388.jpeg, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a_2_1035x582.jpeg 1.5x, https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a_2_1380x776.jpeg 2x" data-small-upload="https://forums.ficsit.app/uploads/default/optimized/1X/dec24f8970f4b5bd73c533bce83aa51b8b72679a_2_10x10.png"><div class="meta">
<svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-far-image svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#far-image"></use></svg><span class="filename">20200623222219_1</span><span class="informations">2560×1440 630 KB</span><svg class="fa d-icon d-icon-discourse-expand svg-icon" aria-hidden="true"><use xlink:href="#discourse-expand"></use></svg>
</div></a></div></p>
<p>Thoughts?</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 2</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-prebuilt-conveyor-belt-curves/675">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-prebuilt-conveyor-belt-curves/675</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 20:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-675</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/suggestion-prebuilt-conveyor-belt-curves/675.rss">[Suggestion] Prebuilt conveyor belt curves</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Existing Mod &quot;slowItDown&quot;</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Shorty66666 Shorty66666]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/shorty66666">@Shorty66666</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Hi all<br>
I hope the Programmer could read this or some how know the programmer xDaris for the mod.</p>
<p>if ist possible it would be nice to add a feature to the lovely toggler:<br>
currently its flowing items when the toggel is empty and stop when its full.<br>
may be it would be nice to make a negativ button.<br>
thats means  the throttle is closed by Default and will open if the toggel say belt is full (and not by if its empty):</p>
<p>example by a big storage handling to Prevent a storage to over flow and block a mixed incoming belt before.</p>
<p>thanks in advance</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 2</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/existing-mod-slowitdown/636">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/existing-mod-slowitdown/636</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 13:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-636</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/existing-mod-slowitdown/636.rss">Existing Mod &quot;slowItDown&quot;</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Mk2 and mk3 pipes</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Jimbodiah Jimbodiah]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/jimbodiah">@Jimbodiah</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Is there a mod that had pipes with increased flow? The vanilla mk1 is severly limiting, eventhough they increased tank volumes to abotu 4-5x they did not add any decent pipes.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 2</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/mk2-and-mk3-pipes/614">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/mk2-and-mk3-pipes/614</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 14:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-614</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/mk2-and-mk3-pipes/614.rss">Mk2 and mk3 pipes</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Few ideas for the Elevator Mod</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asidscript Asidscript]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/asidscript">@asidscript</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>It would be nice if there were no raised fences on the elevator, if there was the option to just have a square foundation, this way the explorer car could be driven on to it and elevated.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<p>would be good if a few square foundations could be snapped to together to make a larger elevator.<br>
so that trucks could be elevated.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>when setting the floors and hights, it would be nice if you could hide the numeric hight section after your settings have been saved. and it would be cool if "during the creation of floor names and hights, that the entery could be drag and droppable. so that its easy to reorder floors if you have some above you and below you.</p>
</li>
</ol>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/few-ideas-for-the-elevator-mod/575">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/few-ideas-for-the-elevator-mod/575</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 15:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-575</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/few-ideas-for-the-elevator-mod/575.rss">Few ideas for the Elevator Mod</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Opening and Closing Doors</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@asidscript Asidscript]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/asidscript">@asidscript</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Hi Guys, One Mod I have not been able to find, Not sure if it exists or not, Is doors. I would like to see open / closable, slidable doors. If anyone is able to make such a mod that would be fantastic.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 2</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/opening-and-closing-doors/574">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/opening-and-closing-doors/574</link>
          <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 15:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-574</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/opening-and-closing-doors/574.rss">Opening and Closing Doors</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>QOL Improvements to the Resource Scanner</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@TheShadoWZYE The Shado Wzye]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Suggestions &amp; Ideas</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/u/theshadowzye">@TheShadoWZYE</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Would be nice to have a little mod to modify the RSS Scanner behaviour such that if a deposit has a miner on top, it get’s ignored thus not showing up. That way we don’t walk in circles in order to find new deposits. No idea how complicated that is in terms of modding or if it’s even possible, but maybe someone with some modding experience wants to have a look. <img src="https://forums.ficsit.app/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=9" title=":slight_smile:" class="emoji" alt=":slight_smile:"></p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 3</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/qol-improvements-to-the-resource-scanner/555">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>https://forums.ficsit.app/t/qol-improvements-to-the-resource-scanner/555</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forums.ficsit.app-topic-555</guid>
          <source url="https://forums.ficsit.app/t/qol-improvements-to-the-resource-scanner/555.rss">QOL Improvements to the Resource Scanner</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
